<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Woodworking on Simon HW</title>
    <link>https://no1ofinterest.github.io/tags/woodworking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Woodworking on Simon HW</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>hathoutwillard@domain.com (Simon Hathout Willard)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>hathoutwillard@domain.com (Simon Hathout Willard)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 18:28:32 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://no1ofinterest.github.io/tags/woodworking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Other Laser Cutting Projects</title>
      <link>https://no1ofinterest.github.io/post/otherlaserstuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 18:28:32 -0500</pubDate><author>hathoutwillard@domain.com (Simon Hathout Willard)</author>
      <guid>https://no1ofinterest.github.io/post/otherlaserstuff/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve made a number of laser cutting projects while at Northforge, and not all of them are large enough to fill a full article.&#xA;My first project was to create a finger-jointed box to store some of my sewing and cross stitch supplied in. It was fun modelling the parts in Fusion, as I got to take advantage of the Mirror and Slice tools to speed up my workflow and ensure everything fit together correctly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making a Laser Cut Map using CorelDraw</title>
      <link>https://no1ofinterest.github.io/post/lasercutmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 13:53:49 -0500</pubDate><author>hathoutwillard@domain.com (Simon Hathout Willard)</author>
      <guid>https://no1ofinterest.github.io/post/lasercutmap/</guid>
      <description>I have seen many laser cut maps for sale at farmers markets and gift stores, but given that I have access to a laser cutter though Northforge, I decided to make my own. The main guide I followed was this one , but it uses Adobe Illustrator, which I do not have a licence for.&#xA;I adapted the process to work using CorelDraw, which is the vector drawing software Northforge has, and also is the software set up to export to the laser cutting machines in the facility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIY Cross Stitch Stand</title>
      <link>https://no1ofinterest.github.io/post/xstitchstand/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:37:38 -0500</pubDate><author>hathoutwillard@domain.com (Simon Hathout Willard)</author>
      <guid>https://no1ofinterest.github.io/post/xstitchstand/</guid>
      <description>For the past few years, I&amp;rsquo;ve been cross stitching as a way to relax. I like how I can follow a pattern someone else created, listen to some music, and eventually end up with a beautiful piece of art to display. Below are a few of the pieces that I’ve made. Patterns are from DMC, as well as this book.&#xA;However, I’ve found my hand gets tired after holding the hoop for a long period of time.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
